Heavenly Father, today we put on the full armor
to protect us against attack. We put on the belt
of truth to protect against lies and deception. We
put on the breastplate of righteousness to protect
our hearts from the temptations. We put the gospel
of peace on our feet to walk in your light, peace,
and freedom with the Holy Spirit. We rebuke
anxious thoughts. We take up your shield of
faith for protection to block and destroy all
the darts and threats thrown at us by the enemy.
We put on the helmet of salvation to cover our
minds and thoughts, reminding us that we are
children of a mighty king. We are forgiven, set
free, saved by the blood of Jesus. We take up the
sword of the spirit, your living word that has the
power to demolish strongholds and is sharper than
any double-edged sword. We come to you, Lord, in
prayer daily. In Jesus mighty name we pray. Amen.
What's up you guys? Welcome to the Imagination.
I'm your host, Emma, and today I'm absolutely
honored to have back on the show operational
CIA monarch mindslave, survivor, overcomer,
and whistleblower, devoted husband and loving
father, blogger and content creator, published
writer and author, podcast regular, and one of our
most requested guests, and a bright light in the
darkness, J.R. Sweet. A little bit about J.R. if
you've missed his other episodes discussing his
harrowing and inspiring testimony or if you guys
are new here. Raised in a family steeped in the
occult, J.R.'s childhood was a labyrinth of abuse
orchestrated by the CIA's MK Ultra and Monarch
programs designed to create dissociative identity
disorder through trauma- based mind control. From
birth, he was sub subjected to incestuous ritual
abuse intended to fracture his psyche and mold
him into a programmable mindslave. The abuse
cloaked in the guise of religious and familial
tradition was perpetuated by a network
that included the LDS church in Disney,
which JR identifies as hubs for programming
and child exploitation. His family's lineage,
intertwined with elite bloodlines, ensured secrecy
through generations with orchestrated ritualistic
abuse designed to manufacture terror and
loyalty to the group's ideology. J.R.'s
Memories of these atrocities were buried under
layers of dissociation until he was in his 30s
when the truth began to surface like fragments
of a long-forgotten nightmare. The awakening
was agonizing, confronting the reality of his
family's involvement in MK Ultra, the cover-ups
within religious institutions and the betrayal of
those he trusted. Yet in this reckoning sparked a
transformation. Jr. turned his pain into purpose,
launching his website and blog www.mormonarch.com
which has become an incredibly important space
where he meticulously documents and shares his
experiences exposing the intersections of MK
Ultra, satanic ritual abuse, and institutional
complicity. His writings are both harrowing and
inspiring, offering a raw, unfiltered look at
the mechanisms of control and the path to healing.
Through appearances on podcasts such as this one,
J.R. has shared his testimony with unflinching
courage, detailing the testing and programming
protocols for children and monarch, the role of
institutions, the government and satanic cults
and organized child abuse and exploitation, the
psychological toll of did and so much more. His
accounts reveal a chilling reality. the federal
government's involvement in child slavery, the use
of dissociation to create compliant slaves, and
the systemic coverups that protect perpetrators.
Yet J.R.'s narrative is not one of despair. His
faith, resilience, and commitment to his family
anchor him as he navigates the complexities of
recovery, using his platform to empower others to
break free from their own silence. J.R.'s advocacy
extends beyond storytelling. as a published author
of his new and incredible memoir named after
his blog's namesake, The Mormon Monarch. His
book further amplifies his message, offering hope
to survivors of ritual abuse and mind control.
His work challenges the stigma surrounding DID and
PTSD, emphasizing that healing is possible through
acknowledgement and community. He confronts
the societal denial that dismisses survivors
as conspiracy theorists, drawing parallels
to the satanic panic of the 1980s, which just
like with MK Ultra, contained kernels of truth
obscured by tons of disinformation. J.R.'s voice
is a counterpoint to the skepticism grounded
in lived experience in a deep understanding
of the psychological and historical roots of
his trauma. His mission is clear. to shine a
light on the darkness, to expose the networks of
power that thrive on secrecy, and to spare future
generations from the horrors he endured. J.R.
speaks not just for himself, but for the countless
children still trapped in similar systems, urging
survivors to reclaim their own power by speaking
truth. His blog and podcast appearances are
a lifeline for those grappling with their own
suppressed memories, offering validation, and a
road map to recovery. Despite the personal cost,
familial estrangement, societal gaslighting, and
the weight of revisiting trauma, J.R. remains a
warrior driven by a moral imperative to protect
the vulnerable. J.R.'s story is a triumph of the
strength of the human spirit in a narrative of
breaking free from the chains of mind control to
become a beacon of hope. His courage in naming the
unnameable, Disney, the LDS church, and the CIA,
for example, challenges the fabric of secrecy
that protects abusers. To survivors, he offers
a powerful message. You are not your abuse. Your
voice can dismantle the darkness. Through his love
for his family, his faith, and his relentless
pursuit of justice, J.R. transforms pain into
purpose, inspiring a movement to end the cycles
of abuse and empower survivors to rise as warriors
of truth. Before wrapping up the introduction of
today's guest, I'd like to share just a couple of
quick reminders and updates. If you're interested
in being a guest on the show, if you wanted to
share any information privately with me, or if
you interested in submitting a written testimony
for my upcoming book series, or to be featured on
a Substack article, you can reach out to me via
email at imagine a better world2020@gmail.com or
standby survivors at protonmail.com. Additionally,
I've teamed up with a couple of my favorite
brands to offer you guys exclusive discount
codes on products I love, such as RIFE Technology
Frequency Machines and CZTL's Premium Methylene
Blue. You can find all the relevant links and
codes along with other resources down below in
the show notes. Your support across all platforms
is greatly appreciated, especially as I've had to
shift to alternative streaming platforms such as
Rumble NX following the extreme censorship that
caused my last YouTube channel to be terminated.
I've just recently started a new YouTube channel
and you can subscribe to me there at the handle@
imaginationodcast official that I am now streaming
new episode episode premieres from weekly. This
transition of multiple platforms is crucial to
continue sharing vital information with the public
and disclosure community. So thank you all on the
other side of the screen wholeheartedly for
helping to make the imagination the safest
space on the internet for survivor whistleblower
advocate and educator disclosures. Your support
means the absolute world to me and to every guest
on the show. So you guys, without further ado,
please help me in welcoming back today's guest
of honor. Monarch survivor and whistleblower,
walking miracle, overcomer, educator, content
creator, voice for the voiceless, anti-child
abuse and survivor advocate, absolute inspiration,
someone I'm honored to call a friend, and a man on
a mission to expose crimes against humanity being
committed on innocent children and humans by our
governments, corporations, and religious
institutions. The one, the only JRu. Jr.,
thank you so much for being here with us today.
It's an honor to have you back. Thank you, Emma.
It's wonderful to see you again. Yeah. Thanks
for having me on as well. I appreciate it. I
appreciate you giving a voice to these things. So,
thank you. It's my honor. If you can live through
it, survive it, and then on top of that, have the
courage to come share. The least that we can do is
support you and listen. This is really important.
the things that you and others are talking about
to help lift that veil off that has been so
tightly bound on people's eyes. And luckily,
so many more people are willing now to start
peeling that away. You know, they're not just
keeping it on. A lot of people now are starting to
acknowledge that these things could have happened
and still are. And it's really wonderful to
see the support of survivors that is sort of
unprecedented. You know, we haven't seen this ever
in history. So, it's it's amazing that we can come
here and talk about these hard things and have
reception from the public. We can give support
to survivors. So, many more are waking up quicker
and quicker and even younger and younger. And it's
really important that we empower people helping
survivors to know this information and that we
give survivors the safety to know how to navigate
these really hard things that they're contending
with that can be so obscure and confusing and
horrifying. So, you're so courageous for speaking
on this and my audience just absolutely loves
you. You're one of our most requested guests.
I get outreach all the time on the difference that
you've made with helping people reckon with this.
And a lot of people appreciate your gentle nature
and talking about such horrible things in a way
that that they can continue listening to. It's
not it's not spoken of in a way that is without
love and compassion. You really keep that in
your heart and and it shows in your message.
So, it's wonderful to have you back and I'm going
to let you sort of lead the conversation. Um,
we have a lot of important things to talk about
today and um sort of I guess how I can um share
a big picture maybe is we're just going to kind
of lay the foundations of of all of this of of
your lived experiences and and that of so many
others and help share how this kind of all fits
together in a lot of different ways and different
layers. And I think you're you do a really great
job of of doing that for us and sort of connecting
the network together, this tapestry that can be
so overwhelming for people to take in. Yeah, it's
all very overwhelming. So, we'll try. I have some
things I want to convey today. I'd just like to
talk to folks about. So, thank you again, Emma,
for having me on. Truly, thank you. Thank you for
being here. Yeah, you got it. I appreciate it. I
want to give people a warning uh particular to
survivors before we really dive into it because
these things can be triggering to people and if
you're a survivor and you're watching this show,
uh please be aware of that that these things can
be triggering and that could be a bad thing for
you. So be aware of that. And folks should be 18
or older who are going to be listening to this.
We're going to talk about some very sensitive
things that are for mature audiences. So I
like to let folks know that before I really
get started. Just a warning. We're going to
talk about some heavy heavy [__] So why am I
here, Emma? I'm here because um because of who I
am. It's not that I don't want to be here talking
with you in particular. I do enjoy talking to you,
Emma. I think you're a wonderful person, but
I wish I didn't have to be. I wish that I wish
that this was not necessary at all. Um but it is.
It is necessary. I'm here because I'm blowing the
whistle on the Central Intelligence Agency's
trauma-based mind control program. My hope and
my goal is to raise conscious awareness in the
people in the population to what's actually going
on in our world and in our government and with
these agencies, the CIA in particular. And if
we can raise awareness and we can raise people's
uh consciousness and their knowledge of this then
then we can bring an end to it. People can decide
that they do not want to support this that they
they don't want to support the corporations that
are doing this or the politicians or the various
networks and religions that are involved in this.
And so they can't make that decision unless they
know what's going on. This stuff's very sensitive.
It's it's highly classified and considered top
secret and and that's nice and all, but it's
illegal. It's unconstitutional. It's a it's an
awful thing that they're doing. And so, regardless
of how they classify it, we need to talk about it.
It needs to be exposed and it needs to come to
an end. So, that's why I'm here. Um, I'm not a
big look at me kind of individual. I just like to
live my life. I like to do my job. I like to raise
my family. And I'm not I'm not doing this for a
show. I'm not doing this for attention. I'm doing
this because it matters and because people have to
understand me and learn about it. And I've made it
this far. And so it's important to me that this
information gets in. So who am I and why should
you be listening to what I'm even saying? That's
a really good question and the inquisitive mind
should ask that. You should learn to ask those
kinds of questions. And so I'm here because I'm
a survivor of the Central Intelligence Agency's
traumabased mind control program. It's a lot to
take in. I understand the need. But people need
to learn to take it. A survivor of the Central
Intelligence Agency's traumabased mind control
program. So the way that that came about is I was
born into a ancestral satanic family bloodline. My
particular bloodline was hiding in uh the Mormon
Church, the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day
Saints. And that's a good place for them to hide
because not a whole lot of people would even
think about that. That's becoming less and less
so as time goes on and more and more is coming
out about satanic ritual abuse. Uh in particular
there in Utah around the Salt Lake area. There's
more and more always coming out and you can watch
what what just went down there and you can see
the corruption that takes place there and how
that church that church owns Utah. It it has is
a huge power base there. So my family was hiding
in the Mormon church. Some of them still are.
Some of my family members have left the church.
But that's how I was raised was as as a kid as a
Mormon. And I thought my life was pretty normal
till 2017 when I started to remember all these
things. It it was far from normal. So a lot of the
things I couldn't remember I there was a reason
I couldn't remember. They have a process to that.
So, I was born into a satanic family bloodline
that's connected uh back to King Henry VIII,
Emma. It goes way back. And if people research
and learn about the bloodlines and the importance
of those bloodlines within the satanic elite,
they'll be able to research that particular
bloodline and gain an understanding of it. I've
been working on that, but I can't share too much
about that yet because I'm not done with my
research. So, but there's reasons that they
were interested in my family. Our bloodline is one
of them. And so, the f because the I'm sorry, the
federal government, they have a big interest in
those bloodlines for a lot of different reasons.
agencies like the Central Intelligence Agency and
even the Pentagon, they have interest in it and
the White House. And there's a lot of reasons for
that. One of the reasons is that we're um really
useful for dissociation. That's what I'm going
to cover more in this conversation. There's other
reasons, but like I said, people should research
that and they can learn the relationships of um of
the satanic leader and the satanic loved ones. So,
I would highly recommend them. One avenue that's
really helpful, Emma, is Fritz Spring Meyer. Have
you ever heard of Fritz Springmemmer? Yeah. So,
he does a really good job of breaking all that
down. and he's actually if you go to the CIA's
website, you can download some of his work there
because it's just information that is out there
and and it's it is what it is. People should
read it and they should understand that. So what
I'm going to cover mostly though is dissociation
because um that's a very important key component
in monarch programming or also known as trauma
based mind control programming. So dissociation
is stronger in people who have uh who
come from a generationally abusive family.
I come from a generational incest incest
generationally it's hard to say it alto together a
generationally incestual satanic family bloodline.
So my family um is very abusive and it has been
for generations and it's tied in the bloodlines
back to King Henry VIII which opens up a whole
other door and so we were abused as children.
I was abused. My siblings were abused. This
is verbal abuse. Um this is mental abuse. Most
importantly, this is sexual abuse and physical
abuse. And those things are traumatizing for a
child. My understanding is the most traumatic
thing a child can go through is sexual abuse,
incestual sexual abuse. And it causes in the human
mind which cannot take that kind of abuse, that
kind of pain, it causes the mind to dissociate
where your conscious mind essentially leaves and
your subconscious steps in. And that's what the
CIA is interested in and the feds is that void
where consciousness steps out and they're able
to step in into that subconscious realm and build
various personalities for various different things
within that individual in that subconscious
place. That's something that's very important.
So, like I said, my siblings were abused. My
father was abused. My grandfather, I believe,
was also abused. He would tell me stories of when
he was a child. And it sure doesn't sound good.
And my grandfather, I believe, is really where the
Central Intelligence Agency steps into this in my
life is through my grandfather and his military
connections. So, we're going to mostly be talking
about the CIA today. I have a relationship with
the Mormon church as well, Emma. I was raised
Mormon, like I said, and that church is being
controlled by a satanic cobble that is connected
to the central intelligence agency. The Mormon
church is very effective through its genealogy
work of locating bloodlines, these satanic family
bloodlines. And they actively work at covering up
ancestral pedophilia, abuse, murder, etc. within
their own community. And then the CIA is able to
select individuals out of that pool that are
useful for them in Monarch programming and in
the trauma-based mind control program. And then
after that an individual has been programmed,
they're useful as a traumabased mindslave. And
then after they become a traumabased mindslave,
they can be be used for other things
such as assassinations, pornography,
child pornography, drug smuggling, various
operations that the CIA is carrying in. And so
I love my country. I've said that before
in our last podcast and I don't know if
people can understand that how someone
could live through what I live through
and still love my country. But it's not my
country that did to me what was done. It
was it was individuals in our government
that are hiding there who are very evil
people and are very nefarious in their
trade. What they're doing is horrible.
They want to destroy our government. They do not
like the democracy that America is. And they want
to enslave the people and they want power and
those people need to be removed from government.
These government programs need to end and these
things need to be exposed because these people
are traitors. Traders against people. They're
traders against the children of the people.
it has to end. And so I love my country and I'm
fighting for my country and my people by raising
my voice on these things. Not trying to make
show. I'm not trying to get attention. I am trying
to help my country, exposing what is wrong and
what is going on. So I just want people to know
them. I love the people of this country. They've
traveled all across this country from west east
and it's just terrible what they're doing.
And I want people to be able
to understand and to know
because we're not talking about me, just
me. We're talking about a lot of people.
My friends were in trauma-based mind
control programming. Not all of them,
but some of them. Some of them are dead now.
Some of their parents are dead because they
found out about it. So, this is important.
This is highly classified and top secret
information. And it's crimes against humanity.
It's crimes against the children of humanity.
These crimes are being committed
by the government. Like I said,
Central Intelligence Agency, Pentagon, the White
House is involved with this [__] Corporations
are involved. The Disney Corporation in particular
was a big one in my life. Religious institutions
such as the LDS church, the Mormon church are also
involved. There's a lot of other people involved,
a lot of different avenues for moving money, for
moving people, for programming. I was put through
Monarch programming in a lot of different
places. One of them was Disneyland. You'd
be programmed with dis Disney films. Those were
great for updating you. You'd be programmed at
Disneyland. And then when you went home all
that year, you'd be watching watching Disney
cartoons. And those were updates for us. I was
programmed on military installations. I remember
being programmed in Fort Worth, Texas. Can be
remember being programmed in Idaho. The Idaho
National Laboratory is located in southern Idaho.
It's covered up under the energy department.
These things are being sponsored by our government
as CIA. Our tax dollars are paying for it as well
as money that's black money that they earn through
selling cocaine, selling people, various means.
And it's just disgusting. So the reason that I'm
here is because trauma based mind control the CIA
was doing that everyone talks about MK Ultra back
in the day everyone knows it as they were testing
people with drugs and they didn't know it and
well they never ended that project. That's a
bunch of BS. It's ignorant. It's naive and it's
dangerous to believe that they did because they
didn't. They didn't end it. Russia didn't end
their trauma-based mind control program. China,
North Korea, this is a thing that is occurring
across the world. People have to wake up to it.
You won't you won't be able to stop this behavior
until you do it. It's a weapon. It's a weapon
being used against the people of this country
and being used against people of the world. And
it's bad. It's a bad thing. It destroys
lives. Emma, you and I were talking when
we first before we we got on the air here
about how it destroys families. It just
tears families apart. These families, they
they perceive that they're a healthy family,
but there's all these things in them that are
nagging away at them all. They're involved with
horrible things and they can't even remember it.
And it's just so destructive from so many angles.
It's also used against people and physical acts
such as mass shootings. People think these mass
shootings are just random acts that are occurring.
They're not just random acts that are occurring.
Not all of them. Some of them I don't know the
answer to. Some of them may be random acts.
There's a lot of them that aren't that aren't
random acts and they're being committed by our
own government against the people in order to push
the people through trauma. It's it's horrible and
it's a continuation of trauma-based mind control
from an individual to a collective level. And it's
being used against people, everyday people. And
people need to understand that it's being used
for assassinations. It's being used to make
kitty porn. It's being used to smuggle drugs
that the CIA makes money on and individuals in
the agency make money on. The satanic elite,
you know, people, a lot of people use drugs.
And the satanic elite, the elite, the rich,
they are no different than than the normal people
in in their desire to do the same thing. Well,
the CIA, they provide them with their drugs. What
better way to know that you're getting a clean
slate of cocaine than to have the CIA provide it
for? So, it's a bad deal. It's got to be exposed
and it's got to end. I know there's a lot of
people who have been reading on this subject,
Emma, and who who know what we're talking about,
but there's some people who don't know what we're
talking about. This might be the first time
someone has seen a video like this, has seen
someone talk even talking about these kinds of
things. And so what we're talking about is called
trauma-based mind control programming. It's also
known as monarch programming. That's a mild way
to put it. Um and it's a form of human slavery.
It is a it is a horrid form of human slavery.
It is slavery. And slavery didn't end with the
13th amendment. A lot of people perceive it did,
but that was that was the ending of the open
marketplace of human slavery. What I'm talking
about is the black market, the black marketplace
of human slavery and human trafficking. We've all
a lot of us have heard about this uh taking
place such as at the southern border where
people are being trafficked. the over 300,000
miners that disappeared to who knows where.
That is the black market of human trafficking.
And the Central Intelligence Agency is involved
with this. Religious institutions are involved
with this. Walt Disney is involved with this. The
Disney Corporation, the CIA, the Pentagon, human
trafficking. And one of those things that they
are really interested in is creating individuals
who are traumabased minds slaves that they can
utilize for various things. And so trauma-
based mind control is is a form of slavery,
but it's involved in the mind in the mind losing
its free will and in an individual essentially
taking over the use of and the use of your mind
and your body through your subconscious mind.
I heard I had remember reading I think it was was
Kathy O'Brien Emma who t discussed in her work
um the human mind being related to a computer.
This makes a lot of sense to me because I grew up
in in a house where my father he owned a computer
business and so computers are very familiar to
me. Now you have in a computer a an operating
system. We have a brain, right? That brain can
be shut off or pushed away, such as if you were
to go around an operating system in a computer.
In that computer or files, various files that can
hold within them different apps. Those apps can be
accessed and used by people who know how to get to
that file and how to know to get to that app. And
that app can be hidden on that computer somewhere
other than say the desktop. And so trauma based
mind control is a lot like that. And what they do
is you are abused from the time that you are born.
I was anyway. So I'm talking about myself now. I
was abused from the time that I was born sexually
um and in various ways. I was made to be involved
with all kinds of things. Sexual abuse was a key
part of it as well as being made to be involved
with uh getting rid of people, killing people,
satanic rituals, things of that nature. These
things drive you to a point of, as we said
earlier, disassociation. When you disassociate,
it's like you've gone around the operating
system of the computer. And so, and you're able to
create a file within that brain, within that mind,
a file that is hidden that only you know how to
access or anyone else who has the keys to that
file within that human mind. So in trauma-based
mind control programming, you are constantly being
traumatized to the point of disassociation where
they are pushing consciousness out of the way and
they are accessing the subconscious where they are
able to create files with all kinds of different
files with all kinds of different uses. And so it
is a lot like a computer. I believe it was Kathy
O'Brien who talked about and so that makes a lot
of sense to me. One of my key programmers growing
up in my life was Dr. John C. Liy and Dr. John
C. Lily, he wrote a book that people can look up
for themselves and they could push purchase it on
Amazon uh at amazon.com programming the human bio
computer. These things are talked about openly in
his book. I don't know if he talks about trauma in
that book, but he definitely goes into discussing
the human mind and the human body as a human bio
computer and how to program that. This man had a
lot of interest in that. And Lily, he was Yeah,
he was not a good person. He really lacked empathy
and and a conscience. And I don't want to get too
much into that, but that is an interesting way
to think about it. But in the end uh through
this process of trauma and disassociation
and accessing the subconscious and creating
different personalities or files as you could
call it in that individual which you can access,
you end up taking away one's free will because
without consciousness and you are operating on
a subconscious basis, you've lost your free will.
People will think, well, how could an individual
be made to do such horrid things? Well, it's it's
simple conditioning in the end. This isn't rocket
science. This is conditioning someone from the
time that they are born to perceive something
as normal and to create that perception
in a space in their mind where they cannot
even conceive that such a thing happened. They
can't even remember it. It's a whole different
part of their mind which they don't access on
a daily basis. It'll nag into you. It'll come
in little snippets into your mind and try to
nag at you, but it's not there on a conscious
level. And so it is a theft of one's free will
through the mechanism of sexual incestual abuse,
molestation, rape, torture, all manner of
trauma including murder and cannibalism. And so
that is the process. Had these
things done to me as a child.
That's how I ended up where I was in the
Central Intelligence Agency and in my
relationship to the Mormon church. These
things were done to cause disassociation
because the things are so bad
and so extreme. Normal people
can't even go there in their mind.
It's so bad and they don't want to.
normal healthy people don't even want to
and I get that but people are going to have
to because there are bad people in the world
and you have to face them and deal with them
so it's a theft of of your free will and with
that I would like to say that it's a theft of
your life your life is taken in traumab based
mind control and your memory of it. You're not
allowed to remember what happened to you. I
can remember being on an operation with my
handler and we were in Japan, which I will discuss
later in this conversation. And my uncle saying,
"It's too bad you're not going to be able to
remember any of this." And it just hitting me
in my mind at that time. even then what do you
mean I won't be able to remember it because I
was in a completely different personality and
that personality was only so old it was created
for what it was doing and it was very confusing
now I understand it but I remember a lot of that
now it can only compartmentalize your memory
and so I don't want to go too much into what
mind control mindbased mind control and MK Ultra
and Monarch programming are. But something I do
want to cover really quick. Um so it is the
process of causing trauma to the point of
disassociation. Once disassociation has occurred,
the subconscious mind has stepped in. The CIA in
particular is looking at that subconscious void,
that subconscious part of the mind, and that's
where they're building multiple personalities and
causing people to and and making people do what
they want them to do. That is how it is done.
The way that they compartmentalize the memory,
they can't erase it entirely, is through various
means. They don't do it just through one simple
means. One of the means, Emma, is trauma. You
know that. Another way is the trauma. I want to
elaborate on that a little bit. The trauma is so
awful and extreme that yeah, it's unfathomable.
Another thing that they do is they will hypnotize
you. Hypnosis is a very important component. I
can remember my grandfather carrying a pocket
watch with him all the time and he would use
that pocket watch for hypnosis. Hypnosis is very
important. Hypnotizing you to not remember things.
If people research into hypnosis, they will
learn that it's not just this thing to be
laughed at. It's a very real science, a
science of the mind. And it is actually
a key component in trauma-based mind control
programming and compartmentalizing that memory.
Remember to forget that memory. Another thing
that they do is they hit you with a stun gun.
There's that physical component to it. So, you've
been traumatized. You have had a program installed
within your subconscious of what you will be doing
for the agency. You will they have hypnotized you.
They're going to hit you with a stun gun. You
pick a spot on your body when you are selected
for the project or being sponsored by the CIA
and you're programming and that spot for me is
on my right thigh and they would hit you there uh
when you were put through a programming session
that just zapped the living tar out of you and
compartmentalized that memory even further. They
have this down to a sentence. So, something that
I find frustrating is when an individual will be
involved with something nefarious, say, let's
just say a presidential assassination attempt,
and their bodies are disposed of weeks after the
event, because their body would have markings on
it that would be clear indicators that they are a
government-owned, a CIA owned asset. trauma-babed
minds slave that's owned by the government,
there would be key markings. I have them on
me and other trauma-based minds I know of have it
on them and if it's just disgusting to see that
because people should know that and they should
start demanding for the that kind of information.
Uh so that is how those things though are
compartmentalized. So they are creating
individuals that they are working for years and
years and years on from the time they're born if
not before and they are working at conditioning
and programming them up through adulthood and
through adulthood even to do various tasks which
are being programmed within their subconscious
mind after trauma has been applied and then they
are eliminating compartment compartmentalizing,
I should say, the memory of those events within
that individual's mind. So, they don't even know
that those things are happening to them or
that they're involved with anything. They
have no idea. Their subconscious mind might nag
at them, but until you have a full awakening of
what was occurring in your life, then you have
no idea who you are, what you were used for,
and there's reasons for people can learn more
about this kind of stuff. Basically, it's a
scientifically engineered nightmare. I don't like
it. It It is very frustrating and infuriating.
And I've had to learn to deal with my anger.
I've had to learn to deal with pain. Um, these
are just things that you have to learn to deal
with. Vengeance is mine, sayaeth the Lord. Don't
want to be like those people. And so just try hard
to deal with them. People want to learn more about
this kind of stuff, they can do research on it.
I don't want to go too ind depth into all that,
but people can do research on it. I have an essay
on my own website. It's called what is MK Ultra?
And people can find that at mormonarch.com if
they want to look at that. Another individual
that you could look into, we've mentioned her,
is Kathy O'Brien. She is a survivor and she
has a story that people should read and people
should understand. And her story is the story
that really awakened me to my past and the
things that I had lived through because of
the connections in her story and my own story such
as individuals such as Bird, Senator Robert Bird,
Charlie Pride, the country musician, and Scars
on My Body, which when I read them in her book,
um took a couple readings over it, but I
discovered I had those same scars and I could
remember the events that caused those scars on me.
So, people should read Kathy's one. Asia Rain is
another individual. She is wonderful person
and people can look up Asia. You can look up
Christy Allen. You can look up Eliza E. There's
a lot of people out there that people should be
should be looking into and should be researching.
You have anything you want to add to that, Emma?
Thank you for sharing and breaking that down.
this stuff as many times even myself as I have
heard this explained in a sense of understanding
that it happens and hearing people talk about it
this process because it was not something I
grew up with. It wasn't something I grew up
knowing existed. You know, I didn't even find out
until my 30s that dissociation existed. I didn't
even know what my body my own body is capable
of doing and how memory is stored. I didn't
understand the different ways that that memory can
be stored, traumatic and otherwise. And it's been
a huge sort of, you know, gut punch for me. Uh,
understanding how skewed our education system is
and how deliberate the intention has been behind
hiding this from us. And it's really important
information. Even if somebody didn't go through
the harsh reality to the degree that you did of
of abuse and trauma, we've all experienced trauma
to some degree. You know, even dissociation has
a sliding scale on how we can experience that
if it's a complete blackout or even, you know,
somebody just feeling dissociated from their
body if they hear of say a death of somebody
that they care about. You know, there's different
ways that we can sort of experience that like
leaving our body feeling of not knowing how to
cope with something that that's happening to us
or something that happens to somebody close to
us, you know, and hearing this, it's just the
more that I hear this information broken down, the
more I'm convinced that, you know, this part of it
is really the most important part, explaining how
this happens. So we can take that information and
relearn how our bodies work and heal ourselves.
You know, especially survivors who have gone
through extreme trauma and fall into that absolute
despair and sadness and anger and all of those
emotions that can come up of feeling that sort
of power and worth taken from you from having
been conditioned. I love that you use the word
condition because that's what it is, you know,
and that can also be hard for people to grapple
with that, you know, even from the the standpoint
of explaining a pedophile, you know, we can people
on the outside look at all of these people and
that's an easy word that we can throw at them, but
when you stand back and understand how this works,
you can see that it's actually conditioning.
People are doing it not necessarily because
they have a sick attraction. And of course people
do, but a lot of this is they're taught that this
is how you raise a child. This is what you do. And
you pass it down to them. You start at this age.
This is what you do. They're trained to condition
a child through doing this. It's not necessarily
like a random assault that we see in the movies
that that's how that happens. It's it's a random
thing. It's orchestrated. It is uh it's it's
planned out like you said from the time that
you're born or even before. and they know exactly
what they're going to do at what age. They then
you're taught, not you, but then the person that
they're doing it to is taught how to do that to
their children. So, it is it's a conditioning
from birth to continue a cycle, you know, and
and so somebody like you comes along eventually
and it doesn't sit well with them. They're
they're unbreakable. they don't conform to it, you
know, and I was saying before we started talking,
you know, I am constantly grappling with that.
What what is it in somebody like you versus all
the other people in your entire lineage that never
walked away from it? You know, what was it in you
that that that caused you to um despite all that
conditioning, the generations of it being passed
down, you know, right in your own family, you had
siblings that went through it. And so thinking,
you know, what is it within a person that doesn't
conform to that and and how special that is that
we have you on the side of it being able to
educate us on it. But I just, you know, going
back to my original point, I really appreciate
you breaking this down because we're taught that
abuse is that the worst abuse that happens is
random. We're taught stranger danger. That we
have to be aware of people that we don't know
around us that can perpetuate danger. And that
that's who is that's who our enemy is. It's not
people that we know and and that are around our
children. It's people that we don't know that are
going to assault us or hurt us. And what we find
through listening to actual abuse testimonies from
victims and survivors is that it's the complete
opposite. There's only a small fraction of these
scenarios that happen randomly. Typically, it's
people that that the child knows. It's family,
you know, which can be and like you said, it's
the most it's the most heinous betrayal. There's
nothing that betrays a child more than a a parent,
especially a parent or somebody in their immediate
family, you know, sexual abuse on them, you know,
and and it's just so foreign to society. So,
this is this conversation is so important. I
just really appreciate how you're able to to put
context and words to it and explain it this way.
Um because it's really, you know, that's the
biggest hidden truth is that trafficking isn't
something that's just of course it's happening
behind the scenes, but they want it to be in
public. They send you to school. They they put
you in public. Like you're not being just hidden
in and abused. You are being abused in private,
but you're living an an entire life publicly and
nobody knows. You're going to church. You're going
to school. And so it's this invisible thi crime
that's happening right in front of our eyes and
we can't even see it because we don't know what
we're looking at, you know. Yeah. You don't know
how to see it. Yeah. Exactly. And to add to that,
a lot of people are involved, including the school
system and your church. For me, that's how it was.
I would go to school and I would be put through
programming at school. They would call it this
special class and you'd be taken back to a room
where it didn't have any windows in it. There
was a two-way mirror and you'd always have to sit
down in this little cubicle and I had this little
uh hourglass that I'd have to turn over and then
there was a device with headphones and I'd have to
put those on but they wouldn't make a sound that I
could hear. It made a sound that you I can't say a
sound. It made it did something I couldn't hear.
And then I had a folder that I was always working
on. I remember that it was like a continuous thing
every year at school. You'd get a folder and that
was your folder for the year and you'd be made to
work through that. And the amount of time that you
had with those headphones on. First time I put
those headphones on, I looked at the gal working
in there and I said, "I can't hear anything. It's
not working." And she said, "No, it's working. You
won't hear it, but it's going into your mind."
And it was this little device that I had to
turn on and put the headphones on. And that room
that was tended by a woman who was some kind of,
you know, she wasn't a teacher. Everyone kind of
referred to her more as like a state employee or
something. I don't know. And but she wasn't looked
at as a normal teacher. And happened at school,
too. Or I was taken to Is that like a gifted and
talented program? I don't know what to call it,
Emma. I remember they said I had trouble with
reading and so I was taken to this other class
where everyone could see you. It was like in the
corner with glass walls and you'd sit there. You'd
always be taken out of your normal class and taken
to this class and then you'd sit down and you'd
work on something and then someone would come
and get you and take you back to that room where
you would be put through that programming.
And so they were able to layer it that way
where everyone thinks you're just going to this
class, work on your reading, but then they come
get you from that class and take you back to the
other room. And so yeah, it happened at school,
it happened at church. Uh bad bad things would
happen at church. They would use it to control
us. Satanic ritual abuse. I can remember being
involved in that as a child. So they control you
through a lot of different avenues. That way they
can enter the full scope of your mind. You're not
safe at home because you're abused at home. Your
parents, grandparents, aunts, uncles, they all
might be abusing you. And then you also include
the school system where you go every day. You
include your church, all those different avenues.
And then your government even is in on it. So, you
know, it's really a mind bender when you're a kid
and you're going through all that stuff. And so,
they use a lot of different faucets and a lot of
different avenues in order to keep control of your
mind and make you feel like it's always hopeless.
You could never raise your voice. You could never
get away. I can remember you can never you can
run but you can never hide. Something like that.
They just ingrain that into you that you can never
get away. You can never hide there. And that's
part of what the harassments are about that they
use for harassing me is to let you know you can't
you can't hide. We know where you are. We know
what you're saying. We know what you're doing. So,
yep.
Reason for it all though, Emma. That's that's
something I wanted to talk about today. You know,
these things are going on. What are they doing
with it? I can talk about what I can remember
in my experience. What they did with me because
throughout childhood I was, you know, tortured,
traumatized, programmed, conditioned to
disassociate. They would program you to do
things. As a kid, I was made to do porn. you know,
kitty porn. It was horrible. And then they would
make you kill people. They would make you indulge
in cannibalism, consumption of human blood. And
all that was working you up in your life to do
something for them later, though. It wasn't just
that they were doing that to have a merry old
time, as sick as they are. It was because they
were conditioning you for when you were selected
for example to be purchased by the agency or when
you are selected for uh special operations
for CIA black ops in particular in my case.
So I was selected for CIA black ops. The man who
selected me was Dick Cheney. Um he wasn't the vice
president yet. He was just going to go work for
Hallebertton when he selected me. He'd just gotten
that job and he was going to be leaving his all
the government stuff for a while and go work for
Hallebertton. And so they wanted to run me through
quick. I was only 17. They really wanted to run
me through because they wanted to ensure that I
would be selected. This was my family pushing it,
my grandfather. And so I was selected by Dick
Cheney. I was made to do some I was made made to
do some awful things. I was tested for my ability
to disassociate and to do what they wanted me to
do. And so in that test, I was made to murder a
girl uh from the local high school here where I
live. And that's a horrible memory. And people
can read about that on my website in my journal
memories. I don't want to talk about it too much
here. Um, it's under Pentagon level testing.
So, I was selected for uh CIA Black Ops because
of my strong ability for disassociation,
my family's connections in bloodlines and
ability to forget things. They they had it
down to a science for my skills at doing what
they had programmed me to do. So I was used
um I was used for a lot of things growing up.
I was used like I said for porn and then I was
used to handle other people in the network. I
just published a memory I had of being involved
with handling Leonardo DiCaprio. People can read
about that in that journal memory. I'm not trying
to gossip about Leo. I just feel like people
should understand that the people in Hollywood,
a lot of them are mind slaves and they're
being used to make money for their handlers
and to create social engineering avenues through
Hollywood. The story is very important that's
carried through the America's psyche and Hollywood
helps to carry that storyline forward. It's very
important for the agency of the satanic elite to
keep everyone moving in the same direction under
the same story line. And so those individuals are
very useful, but it's a sad deal. So I was used to
handle people and I was used to kill people. I was
made to get rid of a lot of people in this world.
I know that I was made to kill over 20 people in
my lifetime which is a horrible horrible thing to
know. One of those people was an individual I was
involved with his assassination. This occurred in
Japan referred to Kobe. Kobe, Japan. And the year
was 1997. It was late August. I was young. Oh,
as a young man then, Emma. And they had decided
that they wanted to use me in that operation.
It was another individual that was a friend of
mine who was mindslave they had considered using,
but they selected me. and so was involved
with that. This was in the murder of Msaru
Takumi of Japan. He's involved in the Yakuza.
You'll have to forgive me. I'm not very good
at pronouncing things, but he's was involved
with a Yakuza called the Yamaguchi. And he was,
my understanding his second in command. was
in charge of money somehow within the Yakuza
and the CIA wanted to get rid of him. The reason
the CIA wanted to get rid of Mr. Kumi was because
he had been involved in funding the 1995 gassing
of the Tokyo subway system. This occurred early
in 95 in the spring. I believe and he I don't
think he knew he had funded such a thing. People
who did that that was the ownio cult out of
Japan there and that cult was an asset of the
CIA. Those people at the head of that cult
were mind slaves, trauma based minds slaves,
and they ended up gassing the Tokyo subway system.
The reason that they did it was to cover up the
economic changes that were happening in Japan at
that time. There were economic changes occurring
in Japan. Something to do with their money. All I
can all I know about that is what I can remember.
some kind of change occurring in the monetary
system in Japan. And the people in Japan,
it had been the way it was for years and they
were resistant to it. And so they caused this huge
traumatic distraction essentially by gassing the
Tokyo subway system and everyone took their mind
off of the economic changes that were occurring
in Japan and they were able to move that through
the system. So, Takumi was inadvertently involved
with funding that culture and the gassing of the
Tokyo subway system. So, he I don't think he knew
it. The money was moved through his mistress whose
brother was Haideki Sel. He's this musicianist.
This guy, this pop guy, I do believe that was
in Japan and he was a big thing. Haidel and he
would move the money to the cult. So he was uh he
I don't know if I could say he was a follower of
the cult but he believed in what it was doing and
he wanted to give money to it donations or so he
thought because Haidico Haidiki Sjo Emma was also
a CIA owned trauma-based mindslave. This is how
all this stuff works. And so the money was being
funneled through this CIA asset, Haideki Sejo, his
sister who was married, who not married. I don't
think they were married. I know he she was his
mistress through her from Takumi. She would ask
him for money to give to her brother and then her
brother would give it to the cult. And then the
cult would use it to do its nefarious things and
to sponsor the cult. And one of the things they
did was buy the gas that they used to gas the
Tokyo subway system. And that gas, I will add,
it's a full circle because that gas was bought
from the United States Pentagon. And so the
money went right back to the damn feds Pentagon.
and they're very smart and they're very cunning
and they know how to work those angles and so they
wanted Takumi dead because they didn't want any of
this to ever come out. When I started to remember
this stuff died of a heart attack within three
maybe four weeks he died of a heart attack. I
felt terrible because I had been remembering these
things. I had talked to some people about it.
They always they're always watching you. And then
later, a couple months later, I believe it was,
they they executed every living member of the cult
that they had in prison. They got rid of them all.
The leader of it, all of them. They killed them
all. It was 12 or 13 of them, I forget. And they
all died. I believe that was in July of that year.
or maybe they did it in two different intervals.
I forget. They killed them all within months of me
remembering these things. And they they wanted
Takumi dead back in 97. They'd wanted him dead
for a while and they'd been trying to figure out
how to do it. But he's he was very powerful man
in Japan. He had his own gang uh that I forget
its name, but he had his own gang and that that
was like a thousand members strong. And then you
include the Yamaguchi Gumi gang, it's huge, one
of the biggest in the world. And so they did not
want this stuff coming out because the CIA um they
could be led to through the through clues and so
they wanted him dead. And so I was brought in as a
shooter in order to be involved with assassinating
Sakun. So the way that this worked, I'm going to
try not to get too indepth into this because I
could talk about this experience for a very long
time, but the way that it worked is I was taken on
a plane from Boisee, Idaho. I would go visit the
airport. I will explain how this occurred. I need
to I need to digress just a little bit. And so at
that time, I believe it was July 1997, I wanted
to go and climb the Grand Teton, this mountain
in Wyoming, the second highest in Wyoming. This
is part of my life, my base personality life. I
wanted to go climb and I was going to spend about
two, three weeks on a climbing trip around Wyoming
climbing various peaks. One of those was the Grand
Teton. My uncle didn't want me gone that long
because we had to train for uh going to Japan and
being involved with Tokumi's assassination. So, he
didn't want me gone that long. So, when my friends
and I left Idaho to go to uh climbing in Wyoming,
we first went to Stanley, Idaho, because my
friend, he had to keep an eye on his sister. That
was the deal with his parents. He had to keep an
eye on his sister for one night because she wanted
to go camping with her boyfriend and stay. So, we
stayed the night there. The next day, my uncle,
before I had left on this trip, had called me,
told me he wanted to talk to me. I was supposed
to stop by his house on my way to Wyoming. So,
after Stanley, we came down from Stanley and
we went to Ketchum because that's where my uncle
lived. It's about an hour south of Stanley. So,
we went down to Ketchum and then Haley, he
actually lived in Haley, Idaho at the time,
which is south of Ketchum and Sun Valley. And
we went to his house. My friends, they stayed
in the car. They didn't I don't believe they came
inside. Not for this conversation because my uncle
talked to me and told me I had to be back after
oh a week or so. He didn't want me gone long.
He said I could climb the Grand Teton and then I
had to get myself back to Idaho because we had to
train for the OP in Japan. So to cut a long story
short, we ended up climbing the Grand Teton. Um
I was able to get back to Idaho. I cut the trip
short uh through various means. People can read
about that in my journal memories on my book or
website. And uh we trained for this operation.
When I got back to Idaho after Wyoming, didn't
have a job because I'd been working at Blimpies.
I was young. I was a kid. Dad, I've been working
at Blimpies making sandwiches. And so I quit my
job before I left because I wanted to be gone and
be carefree for two, three, however long I wanted.
And so I'd quit my job at Blimpies. And when I
came back, my buddy, one of my buddies was wanted
to quit his job at a local Italian restaurant. And
so I was um I applied for that position because it
seemed like it was part of his role to help find
someone to fill that position. He talked to me
about it because he knew I needed a job and I love
pizza and Italian food. I still do today. So yeah,
so I ended up getting a job at Noodles as a pizza
court. With that job at Noodles, I had to train
in Boisee, Idaho. My permanent job was going
to be located in Nampa, the town I lived in,
but I had to train in Boisee. Out of Boisee is
a major airport, and that's where we flew out of
to Japan. So, I would drive to Boisee to go to my
job training. And then my uncle, we would go out a
place called, I believe it was Robi Creek outside
of town, and we would train for this operation up
Roby Creek. And there was another individual
involved. her name was Cat and she would be
out there and she would train with us as well
and I've been working through that more. That's
something I'll include in the second edition of
my book because I've been remembering that and
um that's something I'd like to talk about with
folks because it is interesting and they're
physical locations. I was able to look it up on
Google Earth and be like there it is. There's the
spot right there. That's where we used to train
uh for this operation. And then I can remember
taking various ways out of there. All kinds of
different things. So pretty interesting. Was there
a facility there or anything or was it just a big
chunk of land that was private? It was a big chunk
of land that I don't believe was private. I think
it was public land. Yeah. And we would train for
the pendulum swing off of this giant tree that
was down in the down in this big goalie. and
there was a little bridge across the goalie and
we would practice our pendulum swing there. It's
not always the scale of what you're doing so much
as the process getting nailed down. And so we used
this environment to nail down what's called the
pendulum swing and how we were going to do that
and accomplish that in Japan to move from from one
rooftop of a building to another because we used
the pendulum swing system in order to quickly move
uh through terrain that was difficult and slow to
climb and it was quick way to get from point A
to point B. And so we trained for that up there.
And then my uncle would always also put Cat and I
through some other programming and stuff up there,
but yeah, that's that's a whole different story.
So, we trained up there and then when it came time
to actually go on the operation, we left on the
OP uh the day the last my last day of training
in Boisee, Idaho at Noodles there in downtown.
So, I trained down there for two weeks. During
those two weeks, we were constantly training out
up Robby Creek. And at some time before this,
I see some weird things had happened because the
way that I started to even remember this memory,
Emma, is I could remember going to the Boisee
airport and reading my Bible. I would go to the
Boisee airport, sit in the waiting area and read
my New Testament. And I could always remember that
that I would go there and just sit there and read.
And it was summer, so it was really hot. I had an
old 1966 Volkswagen camper van, and it didn't
have very good AC. It didn't have AC at all,
I don't believe. And so that thing was a
very warm. And so it was nice in my mind.
I perceived it that it was nice to go sit in the
air conditioned airport. It was quiet. I didn't
know anyone in there. No one would bother me. I
was raised in a really big Mormon family. I have
uh four other there's four other kids including
me in the family. And so it was a place I could
find solitude. It was quiet. I could read from my
Bible. This was how I had perceived that. Well,
that wasn't what was going on. I was programmed
to go to the Boyisey airport and sit down and
read from my Bible. I can remember going there,
sitting down, reading from my Bible, getting up,
going to the restroom. When I came out of the
restroom, there were some chairs in front of me
and a table and a plane. And on that table there
with the plant was an airplane ticket. And I said,
"Oh, look, there's a plane ticket." When I came
out and I was really curious and my mind was
nagging at me because I'd been through programming
that this was all going to take place and to make
it go down. And what this was was a test run to
see how I did by myself with no handler present in
them being able for me to go to the location they
needed, sit where they needed me, be dressed how
they needed me, and then for them to come and get
me and get me on my flight uh over to Japan. And
so this was a test run. So I sat down next to this
airplane ticket and I was really curious about it.
I didn't touch it for a while. I just kind of
sat there. And then after about 10, 15 minutes,
I was like, "Well, no one's coming." At least I
think that's how much time passed. No one's coming
to get it. And so I picked it up and started to
look at it. Well, it was already expired. So I
was like, "Yeah, someone just left their plane
ticket." So I got up and I drove back to my my
parents house where I live. Well, I can remember
going through um meeting with my uncle and giving
him that ticket and having followed my orders and
my directive and him being very happy with me. And
um the next time I would go to Japan, it was uh
for the operation. It was we're going out of town.
And so it was my last day working in Boisee.
I can remember driving over to Boyisey and I
could hardly see. My eyes were so sensitive that
morning. I had these sunglasses. They were round.
They're like John Linen sunglasses and they were
red and I was wearing those driving my van over to
Boisey, you know, as this little hippie looking
kid. And um I could hardly see though. My eyes
were so sensitive. And it's most likely because
of the programming that I've been put through the
night before and the electrocution. But I drove
over to Boyisey. I went to work. Another thing I
experienced that day was my body temps were off.
I can remember wearing a sweater. And this was
in August in Boisee, Idaho. It is so wicked hot
in Boisee, Idaho in August. and I was wearing a
sweater and I was going to do the lunch shift
and so I went to work. I had to walk there. I
parked at an Albertson's in town because it was
hard to park in downtown Boisey and then I had to
walk and so I'm walking down the street with this
black sweater on of all things and I went to work
and I can remember that day at work I was off and
my coworker who had been training me for the two
weeks was like what's wrong with you? you know,
and I just told him I was tired. And I told him
how excited I was to go to the Boisee airport and
to sit down and read my Bible. And he thought that
was very strange. He was he didn't know what to
make that I think he just figured I didn't feel
well. And I told him I didn't feel well. all. And
so after work that day, I left and I walked back
over to my van and I went straight to the Boisee
airport and I got a ticket for parking because you
had to get a ticket for parking and that's one of
the things that's one of the clues that G gave all
this away to me. Um almost gave it all away in the
experience. their mind control programming is very
strong. And all this didn't come together until
I started to journal this out. And so I got a
parking ticket and I went inside and I went and I
parked my van. Now I was wearing work clothes. I'd
brought a change of clothes and so I changed into
other clothes. I had a white shirt much like this
one, just a white shirt. And I had a belt buckle
that I had gotten on a trip with my grandparents
back east. The trip where I met Charlie Pride,
met with Bird. And I'd gotten this belt buckle
at a a war memorial. It was a battlefield of
some kind. I haven't journaled all that out. I
just remember getting this Civil War belt buckle.
It said Us dot on it. And it was this big cowboy
style replica of a Union soldiers belt buckle.
And I also had a belt that had my grandfather's
name on it because they'd used different aliases
for me. My alias was Mark on that trip. And so
that was interesting. And then I had my John
Lennon sunglasses on. And we I went inside,
park my van, go inside, go up and I sit down and
I got my Bible and um I don't know how long I sat
there. there. I read my Bible for a little while.
Then I put it down and I don't know how long I was
there just sitting there watching the planes and
then my uncle came came from behind me and he was
with another gentleman and it was like oh hey
you know at first you're like oh hey what are
you doing here? I remember being really messed up
that day because I swallowing the program and so
it seems like I was moving through personalities
even as all this was going down and I saw my uncle
and you know even people can be a trigger in
these things. People talk about using words for
triggers or hand symbology for triggers but even
seeing an individual in a certain situation can
be a trigger. So I remember my uncle came. He was
with this gentleman who was the luggage handler.
He was in charge of the luggage handling in the
airport, the boyisey airport. And my uncle told
me I had to go with this guy and because we had
to go load up the plane. And so me and this guy,
I don't remember his name, but he was a bigger
gentleman, probably in his I would say early
early 30s, I would say. and maybe late 20s and
he I went with him and we walked through the
back ways of the airport. I don't even know how
to describe it because I don't remember a whole
lot of getting there. I just remember we took
the back ways and then we were in a room with
a big roll up door and there was a cart that you'd
load up luggage on that you always see in like the
movies or if you go to the airport they have
these carts that haul your luggage around to
the plane and there was this luggage cart and we
loaded up this luggage cart because the central
intelligence agency used the boyisey airport. They
controlled the people who own the Boyisey or who
they controlled through blackmail the people who
are in charge of operating the Boisee airport.
And so this uh Boisee airport is an asset to
the Central Intelligence Agency and they were
able to store items that would be used globally or
domestically in that airport at a back part of the
of the luggage department. And so we we loaded all
of our gear for this operation we were going to do
over in Kobe, Japan. We loaded it all onto these
carts and then we flew or we loaded it all on the
carts and then we took it out to the plane. Now
during this process, I can remember uh some key
events occurring. So this individual, this luggage
handler, he smoked cigarettes. And then this other
guy who was his minion of sorts, also smoked
cigarettes. And the younger guy asked this older
gentleman if he couldn't bum a cigarette. And
I saw this occur. And there's a part of me that
enjoys smoking cigarettes. And because I've been
made to do so since I was a child, that was part
of my programming actually. Uh, I can remember the
first cigarette I had was in Disneyland. And so I
asked too, can I have a cigarette? I I wouldn't
mind one, you know. And so we both we all three
had a cigarette. We're loading the plane and well,
time passed and this uh younger gentleman said
to the older gentleman, "Um, can I buy another
cigarette?" and he promised he'd buy him more the
next day because you could see this was going to
be a continual thing for the two of them because
the other guy he couldn't afford to buy him that
day or something. He didn't have any, but they
were both chain smokers. And so, so then I asked,
"Can I bump a cigarette?" You know, and at first
he was a little frustrated and he started to give
me one and then he said, "No, I'm not giving you
one." He said, "You're a chosen one. You're not
supposed to have one." And then he put it away
and he lit up his own and he he became very angry
and he started to tell this other guy who worked
for him about who I was as a mindslave. And this
young guy, he was just like, "What is going on?"
He had no idea, you know, and this guy saying he's
traum based mindslave. Uh he was abused. You know,
people know about this stuff and they don't talk
about it. It's they know about it. And so he was
talking about me right there in front of this guy.
And I just was dissociated from the situation. I
just started to dissociate deeper. Because I was
already in an operational personality. And this
guy said, "Watch, I'll show you. He can he can
deal with pain. Watch what happens when I burn him
with my cigarette." And he pulled my shirt open
and he took his cigarette cherry and he pushed it
into my chest right over here. and he burned into
my chest with his cigarette cherry. And I was I
just disassociated from the situation because
that's what you do when you're a traumas based
mindset. I just dealt with the pain. I didn't
do anything. I just sat there and let him burn
a hole in my chest. And then the young guy, he was
just freaked out. Well, it seemed like the older
gentleman realized what he was doing because
he stopped and he pulled the cigarette away.
told me to, you know, do your shirt back up. And
just acted kind of strange like, "Oh [__] what
have I done?" kind of a thing. And so we finished
loading up the stuff and they loaded me on the
cart with the luggage because I was pretty much
luggage for these people. And so they they loaded
me onto the luggage cart and we rode across the
tarmac across the airport runways and we went to
an area believe it was at McGawan Field. See
McGowan Field is located directly across from
the Boyisey airport. They're they're connected
right there. And we rode over to this military
transport plane and it was big plane. Not huge
as I don't think it was the biggest one they got,
but this sucker was big. And they pulled it
around there. We loaded up our gear. Well,
the guy started to load it up. My uncle came
out of the plane. He'd gone around and finished
filling out his paperwork or whatever for getting
the plane. And then we loaded up on the plane and
the other guys loaded our gear and Cat was on the
plane. The guy flying the plane was this guy that
I had seen before um earlier in life. There's
this network of people you're always running
into. And so this individual, I knew who he was.
I'd seen him before. They call him my cousin.
People in the network are of in the CIA network
are often called cousins. you're all a member of
the familia. And so my cousin John, he was driving
the plane or flying it, I should say. And another
individual. And then Cat, she was in the back.
Well, my uncle, he saw my shirt that something
was starting to stain through on my shirt. And he
got really pissed. He Well, he didn't get pissed
at first. He said, "What is that? What happened
to your shirt? What is going on?" And you know,
I was in the state of mind you were in. You did
exactly what you were told. If that included
talking and saying what happened, you said exactly
what happened. I said, "That gentleman out there,
he burned me with his cigarette." Um, and my
uncle just freaked out. He was so pissed when he
heard what had happened because that individual
could have jeopardized the entire operation by
doing that to me by essentially torturing me and
damaging a US government asset. And so my uncle,
he went out and he chewed their ass. And my
uncle when he would get mad, you didn't want
to be on the receiving end. He could get mad. and
he was all coked out because he loved his cocaine,
especially when he was doing operations like
this. And he went out there and he just chewed
that guy's ass. Well, Cat and I, we sat down and
uh Cat bandaged up my my chest. We had to get it
taken care of and she put some kind of an ointment
on it to help it scar less. You can see the scar
on my chest and it's there. It's not as bold as
it could be if they hadn't addressed it, but it's
there. And so then my uncle came back in and he
was all pissed. Said how that guy was all screwed.
And because my grandparents were on a mission
at that time, to add to this, this individual
had not only damaged the government asset, he had
scarred a chosen one because I'm considered what's
called a chosen one. And your scars in particular,
going back to what we were talking about earlier,
are very definitive. And so those scars label
you. And to have someone scar a chosen one,
that's a bad deal. That's a death sentence for
you. If you know better and you do that, you're in
trouble because we would end up uh getting rid of
this individual. When my grandfather, who was also
involved in all this stuff, would come back from
his mission. I believe he was down in Texas and
he came back from his mission later that year in
the fall and we went and we got rid of that guy as
well as his daughter. No one was spared in that.
He had had a daughter with my exgirlfriend because
he had gotten a job at the same furniture store
that I had worked at that my girlfriend's father
owned. And so when I had left this individual, I'm
almost positive he came in right after me and then
he got into a relationship with my ex-girlfriend
because we broke up. And so this guy, he was a
he was very a very forward fellow. And so he
worked his way into her life. They ended up
having a child together. They didn't want her to
even remember having the child, Emma. And so this
child was hidden from even her after it was born.
And um the the little girl lived with this man,
her father, who lived in a trailer in this part
of town that there in Nampa by the Nampa airport
in this manufactured home. And so we'd end up
getting rid of that guy and that little girl at
that time. It was a really bad experience and we I
won't cover that much more than what I just said.
This guy would pay for what he did. And so so we
took off. They would always give me drugs. They
gave me a drug to fall asleep on that flight.
They'd make you sleep through the flights and
stuff. When you weren't being used or operational,
you'd be put to sleep. And so there was this blue
drug. All the drugs that they would give me would
be colorcoded. Uh we call them potions. My uncle
had this little black box that he would keep
them in with this little cork on them and you
drink the potion and stuff was potent. I'll tell
you what, you drink that stuff and yeah, there
was going to be no staying awake for you. And so
I slept on the flight. I woke up on the flight
uh because it wore off at some point. I don't know
where. I just woke up and my uncle, he was abusing
Cat. Cat was this nice uh nice gal. Yeah. From
Europe. I'm not sure entirely where in Europe,
but she was from Europe. And she that's a whole
long story, but he was abusing her. And I said,
"What the hell are you doing?" And he said, "I'm
programming this [__] What does it look like?"
And that was a very bad experience. And I was in
a very bad state of mind. If I wasn't in the state
of mind I carry these days, I would have thrown
his ass right out of that plane. And so that was
a bad deal. He I ended up going back to sleep,
more drugs. We landed in Japan and um when we
landed I was asleep. So I woke up just the plane
was just sitting there and it was darker outside.
seemed really misty and I could hear people and
I was in the black back of the plane by myself
and I looked out the window and I could see these
people out there in these uniforms of some kind
and they were unloading the plane and my uncle was
out there talking to them and I can remember one
of them looking up and saying, "Hey, he's awake."
You know, he's awake. They weren't Americans and
they were Japanese uh is what I would learn as as
time went on. And they were shorter than my uncle,
uh smaller people. And so my uncle, he saw I
was awake and he came in and he administered
more drugs to me. I asked where Cat was. Where's
Cat at? and she'd been sent into the city to work
on setting up for the operation because we we had
to set up a shoot nest where we would shoot from.
They ended up putting me in a piece of mechanical
equipment on a rooftop of a building there in
Kobe. Yeah. Just right inside the equipment and
that's where I I was able to shoot from at the
Oriental Hotel there in Kobe where Msaru was. And
so cat, she was in the city getting set up and my
uncle and I, we ended up coming out of the plane.
The Japanese folks were very respectful. The thing
with it, okay, Emma is these people were also
CIA assets, but the agency didn't control that
airport. To my knowledge, they did not. And so
we had to be really careful getting me into the
airport and getting me through all that because
we didn't want to get caught. And so the people
we were working with, they knew who we were. They
didn't quite understand what we were about. They
perceived it that we were going to kill Msaru and
get rid of that guy. But they didn't understand
that Msaru had been used by the CIA and they were
actually working for the ones that had caused all
the trouble to begin with and that Msaru was just
just someone they were getting rid of to keep it
all secret. They thought he had, you know, fund
they thought that he had funded been involved
with funding that gassing and they were glad to
see him go. That's what they've been told. that
that was not the case. And so we ended up getting
me into the airport that we had to go through the
airport. I was led through the airport by this
young gal, a female there from there in Japan.
And this man that was the head of the luggage
people, uh, a lot of their family, it seemed like,
were working there altogether. And this woman was
involved with that family. and we got me through
the airport and to a spot where they just set
me down in the waiting area in Japan then. So I
just went from Boyisey sitting in the waiting area
reading my Bible. My Bible went the whole way from
work at Noodles to the airport to Kobe. Now here
I am in Kobe. I'm sitting there reading the same
Bible and I'm reading the New Testament and then
my uncle comes up to me and starts talking to me.
And then we went and we had a vehicle waiting
for us. It was a government vehicle and that
um we loaded that with all of our equipment. So we
went from that waiting area to our vehicle which
was just outside, drove it down and around and we
loaded up um the vehicle with all of our supplies,
our equipment, our gear. Uh my uncle had his
cocaine hidden in there. One of the first things
he did, the Japanese folks, they loaded up our
truck for us and I was made to pretty much sit
in the truck. I like to get out and talk to
people and but I was told to just sit in the
truck. I think I got out and then I was told to
get back in the truck. Um then my uncle got out
and he talked to some people and he told him
how I wanted it organized and then he was able
to get his coke. She had a little thing full of
cocaine and then it came up into the front of the
vehicle. And this vehicle had a big compartment
in the back, a big area and then a little doorway
and then our seats up the front and so we could
move back and forth through the vehicle through
it. And so we sat there, my uncle did cocaine and
then he gave me more drugs. It was war on drugs.
You know that when Kathy O'Brien talks about that
war on drugs, she ain't kidding because yeah,
you are so hyped up on drugs. And then we went
from there from the airport loading up our gear
to a warehouse. And at that warehouse, um there
was a warehouse there by the ocean somewhere.
And that warehouse was scheduled for demolition.
And so we went and we went in this warehouse. It
was pretty empty in there. There was a little
bit of stuff in there, but not much stuff.
We went back in there and we parked the van and
then we um Oh, and I remember driving the van. My
uncle made me drive it and I was like, Gail,
I'm so hyped up on drugs right now. How are
How am I supposed to drive this van? And he was
like, just drive. Let's go. You know? Yeah. So,
we're all hyped up on drugs, driving this van
around Japan. And we went to this warehouse
and we parked in there and we ate lunch. Well, I
ate lunch. I can remember eating MREs. My uncle,
he was going to go into the city to meet with
Cat and so he was going to go eat somewhere nice,
but I ate um I ate MREs, I think two of them.
And yeah, just gross food. But then at that time,
that's what that's what you ate, you know. I
didn't even think twice about it. I was like,
"Yeah, give me my MREs." and we unloaded the van.
We had these black hard cases that all of our gear
was stored in. I want to say they're a lot like
what's called, I believe, a Pelican case. These
black hard cases and that's what we stored all
our gear in. And so we got all our gear out of the
van, went through it, put everything in there and
organized it how we wanted it, and then we took
these hard cases that we didn't taking up all the
space in the van and we put them uh we hid them at
the back of the warehouse. So this warehouse was
scheduled for demolition and so people weren't
using it. I can remember the roof was falling in
in part of it. No one would ever think to think in
this dark corner of this place to find this kind
of stuff and they couldn't see us doing it either.
Emma, that's another key is if there were planes,
helicopters, anything in the sky, you wouldn't
see what we were doing or from the sides. We were
well hidden in there. And then I was put to sleep
after I'd eaten my MREs because my uncle had to
go into the city and I don't know how long I was
asleep for. The next thing I remember is waking
up in the van and just it was dark. I was like,
where on earth am I? And I could hear my uncle
and he was talking to somebody over the calm
system in the back of the van. I could hear it
and I started to wake up and I can remember at
that time it was really strange because in that
personality I knew what we were doing. I knew that
my family was involved with these things. I knew
that this is what my family did for the federal
government. That that was our contribution as a
family to the CIA, to the Pentagon, to the feds,
to the White House. that was our contribution is
we went in and we got rid of people and I could
remember all that and that's just how it was. And
some in the family knew and some didn't. Some of
my brothers and sisters have no idea. All of them
I would say in their conscious state of mind and
even in a subconscious state they wouldn't even
know because it would be hidden from them. This
stuff's all compartmentalized even within the
families. But I was a part of that part of the
family where we were used to get rid of people.
And so my uncle was there. He was talking to Cat
on the comm system. Cat was up on the building
somewhere. We were deep in the city of Kobe in
a van in a dark alley. And my uncle got me
moving. He gave me more drugs to wake me up.
Got me all hyped up again on drugs. We got me
into my operational suit. I was made to put on
this one piece suit with no markings. You're not
allowed to have any markings of any kind. This is
just a generic straight suit. It was a one piece
and that was it. I wasn't even allowed to wear
my underpants, Emma, because they didn't want any
anything that could identify you as an individual.
So you were stripped of everything and put into
this uniform with no markings. They did give me
nice boots and then um we were harnessed up
and my uncle he had these devices that were
made for suctioning cupping basically to glass
and we were next to a glass building. We were
parked in the alley by a big glass skyscraper
and we would attach to those suction cups which
were electronically controlled. You didn't have to
sit there and pump it or anything like that. You
put it on and it would attach to the glass. And
then you had a strap with a carabiner that you'd
be able to stand in and you're attached to two of
these. You got two of them. And you'd attach one.
You'd stand up. you'd attach another stand up and
you'd basically be able to walk up the building
this way and I was attached to my uncle. My uncle
did the same thing and we were able to we did a
test first to make sure everything was working and
then up we went and we ascended this building and
it's a lengthy process. It's not super fast. So,
we go up this building and I can remember getting
up there and we reached an area where it was a
divide between two buildings and we had to get
across it. And this is where the pendulum jump
was set up that we had been practicing in the
Boisee Valley. There was this big great big sign
up above on the wall of this giant building and
we were way above the city. I can remember
looking down and I wasn't afraid of heights
in that personality at all. It was like, "Oh,
cool. We are way the hell up here and my uncle,
he called into Cat. She was across on the
other building's uh top and he called into her,
said we were over there. We'd reached that point
and then she came over to where we were." And the
way it worked is you had an anchor point at each
end. So, we had an anchor point where we were and
she had an anchor point on her side and there
were ropes that were connected up above on this
sign and they were tied off right there and you
would swing and come up and land at that anchor
point and you'd set your anchor. Now you're here.
You could release yourself, jump and fall and
come back over to the other side and connect. Now
you're anchored on that side. It was a very quick,
efficient way to move from point A to B. And so we
all did the jump and that was quite a jump. That
was a huge jump. And we jumped through that and
we landed on the other side. And when I landed,
Emma, we had trained for it. When we had trained
in Boyisey, I had landed wrong on one of the
landings and it had tweaked my back. And my uncle
knew this and they knew when it happened because
they'd been telling me to relax. Relax. Relax
when you land because I was so tense. They said,
"You need to relax." And so I was too relaxed and
I strained it in Boyisey during training. And then
on this exercise, I was still relaxed too much and
wham and it hurt my back. And so we got me off of
the line and it had strained it, but I was okay.
I was like, "No, I'm okay. We can still go through
with with operation. You know, I'm not that bad
off." And so we moved across the rooftop to where
we had a shootute nest and that's where they put
me in the piece of equipment up there on top of
the roof. And so they had a big piece of HVAC
equipment and they'd opened one of the louvers
and inside the this piece of mechanical equipment
was a rifle setup and a little area where I could
lay down with that rifle. And so I was placed in
this piece of mechanical equipment and there was
stuff moving around me. You know, it wasn't very
comforting being in there. And I was stuck in
there for I don't know how long hours I was stuck
in this. And it was all night. I don't know what
time of night it was that I got there, but they
put me in this thing. And they sealed it back up,
put the screws back in, and then they left.
They went to their places and that's where I was
stationed. And I was in contact with them through
my comms. I had a little um I had a vial with me,
a vial to wake up. And my uncle gave me gave
me some blue blue potion of sleep before they
closed me up so that I would fall asleep. And
so I fell asleep when they closed it up. And
then when I woke up, the comms were going off.
Something was going on. And I woke up and my
uncle talked to me and he told me to take the drug
I had, the red drug. And I drank the the drug,
the potion they had given to me to wake up and
get operational. And I can remember just being
crammed in this thing. It was hot. It was loud.
It was stuffy. It was awful. But that, you know,
deal you're programmed to deal with that. And so I
was in there and we tested our calms, went through
all that and then it started to get closer.
Now during all of this, my uncle would say,
"I'll be back. I've got to talk to somebody else."
Because he was also in contact with our Japanese
counterparts. There were other people in Japan
working with us. It wasn't just CIA. And so in
all of this, the way the CIA was going to get to
Kumi, Emma, is uh there was a rival gang of the of
the Yamaguchi Gumi known as the Nano Nakano Kai.
I'm sure I'm butchering the pronunciation, but the
Nakano Kai. And they were, I believe, an offshoot
of the Yamaguchi. And they were a violent,
more violent group. and they wanted Tkumi dead for
some reason and they had come to the CIA and they
had asked the CIA for help in killing Takumi. The
CIA who had been trying to find a good way to kill
Tkumi said great, what an awesome opportunity.
They seized on it because now they had a cover.
So you had these four guys of the Nakano Kai
that were going to come in to the Oriental Hotel,
which is where Tacumi was was going to be that day
at that time that we were going to get rid of him.
These four guys come in and they were going
to shoot up the place and I was supposed to
hit Toui through the window uh in the hip as a
sniper to ensure that he was dead because the
manokai was absolutely terrified of Takumi.
if he would have lived through this assault,
those four guys and their leaders, it would
have been held to pay. And so they they wanted
to guarantee he was dead. That's why they come
to the CIA. Can you guarantee he'll die if we do
this? And so they came in from the ground. So I
get woke up and it's gonna happen. It's going to
happen. They're coming in. They're coming in. And
then all hell broke loose out of my scope. Just
seemed like all hell broke loose. I was squared
up on an individual. My optic was uh connected to
a video recorder of some kind that was connected
to a screen in my uncle's van which was down in an
alley there in Kobe. And so he could see through
my scope from his from his van, which would we
would call his command center at that point, see
what I was aiming at. And he directed my aim,
told me who to hit at the moment he wanted me
to hit it. And then I was made to fire. Now,
when I fired, I blacked out. I instantly blacked
out. Boom. Blackout. Gone. When I went hunting,
when uh I was studying at the University of Idaho
later in life, I went out hunting for deer and I
was up on a hill and I squared up on a deer and
I almost passed out. I was like, "Oh my god,
don't pass out. Don't pass out. Don't pass out."
And I could never understand what was wrong with
me. Why would I pass out just from squaring up on
a deer? And that's why because I was programmed
to pass out after I fired the shot. They wanted me
out. They wanted me immobile because I don't know
what the percentages are, but your movement from
your shoot nest is what'll give you away after
the shot is fired. They did not want me moving.
They did not want me mobile. Nothing. They just
wanted me almost like I was dead. I just went out.
I blacked out. The next thing I remember is being
woken up. Now, I want to add I don't know who
I shot. I don't know if I hit the Kumi. I don't
know if I hit another individual. Believe he was
a dentist. Uh his name I believe Hiroshi Huray.
And that individual was killed in the exchange in
the Oriental Hotel. Because when I would talk to
my uncle later in a different memory about this,
my uncle would tell me, "I didn't kill Tumi. I
killed an innocent bystander, a dentist who was
there at the scene. This is what my uncle would
tell me. But I was supposed to kill that man if
I killed." That's who they would have wanted me
to kill. It's a mess. The whole thing is a mess.
They're constantly messing with your head. So, I
was woke up. They got me out of that thing, out of
that piece of HVAC equipment. It was daylight. It
was broad daylight. I said, "What the hell's going
on? It is broad daylight. We are not supposed to
move like this." And they said, "No, we got to
move. We got to move now. there's no time to
wait. The police had already been to the rooftop.
They already knew something was up and they were
going to come back with dogs. And so we had to get
off of the roof fast. This roof had flat spots on
it. So there were spots that were flat where
you could walk on it. And so we got down, we
got off the roof in the descent. So when I did the
pendulum swing this time, it was broad daylight.
I can remember being like, "Oh my, like I don't
know who's going to see this." And just out I
went across this massive expanse of space and
we made our way down. But on my way down, Emma,
there are two individuals out there in the world.
And I pray to God they're still alive. I don't
know who they were. They saw me coming down with
my suction cup devices because that's what I was
using to come down by myself. cat had to go and
start taking stuff apart. She was in charge of
disassembling the whole thing before the dogs and
police came back. And I was going down and these
two individuals I went past their window because
I could see people inside this building as I'm
walking down it with these suction cups and these
two guys open the window and they're yelling at me
in Japanese and they're in suits and I'm hanging
there and I'm in contact with my uncle and I said
there's these two guys and they're yelling at me
and he said tell them you're a window washer. and
he told me how to say it in Japanese that I was
a window washer. I'm a window washer and I told
him that and it didn't seem to satisfy him. They
kept yelling and yelling and waving and I he said,
"Get down. Just get down right now." And so we
got down. Long story short, I ended up getting
out of the city. We left the city. We got back
to the airport. um got back to the airport on the
plane and our the luggage handlers in in Japan,
they thought that we had killed Takumi. You know,
the whole storyline that we'd been there to
kill him and they congratulated us and they
were told they couldn't talk to me. I was made
to get back in the van because I'd gotten out
for a minute and they loaded me back on the
plane and Cat wasn't there. She didn't come
back. She didn't make it back to the plane. And
that worried the [__] out of me. Oh my. We were
close. I I hope she's okay. And we left Japan.
And we left Japan without her. And we flew back
to Boisey. When we got back to Boisey, the older
luggage handler that had burned me with cigarette,
he wasn't there anymore. He'd been fired. And just
the younger guy was there. And we got back over.
My uncle just kept giving me drugs. He asked me
what I wanted because we had our favorite drugs,
you know, the ones we really enjoyed. cuz you're
a mindslave and all that. You've been doing that.
You've been conditioned for that since as far
back as I can remember. It was just potions to
us. So me and the younger luggage handler kid that
had been there before and witnessed these things,
he didn't want to talk to me at all anymore
because the other guy, he was fired. He didn't
know what was going to happen to him. and got we
got back over to the airport to the luggage area
and unloaded stuff and remember being being back
at the waiting area just sitting there reading
my Bible just buzzing hard on those drugs and
my uncle came told me you know you're going to
forget all this you know basically that was it.
Then he left and then I sat there a while longer
and then I left and went out to my van. When I got
to my van, stop in I drove over to the place where
you give your ticket to the parking attendant. I
handed it to him. He told me some amount that I
was like, "What? What are you talking about? said,
'Th that's way too much. How can that be? And he
said, 'Well, you've been here for three days. I
said, three days? I haven't been here for days. I
I as I perceived it, I'd been there for hours.
In my mind, I had started to forget all those
things. All those things were gone. Now I was
just going home from work. I had the weekend off.
I was going to go and just relax for the weekend
before I started my work in Nampa at Noodles.
And no, I paid the bill for parking and I was so
confused. I was like, how can this be? But part of
me just covered it up again. Just it there's they
build personalities in your subconscious that are
layered that one layer wants to cover up the other
layers. And so those layers just help cover it
up and drive home. And as I'm driving home, I'm
driving past the Boisey uh Mormon Temple, another
trigger to forget. And I got home and my buddy
Chris showed up. My buddy Chris Kenudson, he was
the other individual that they were thinking about
using in the in the as a sniper for it. and we
were friends and he was at the house and everyone
was saying that I'd been off with Chris doing
something like all weekend and I was like weekend
I was so confused weekend I was with Chris and the
whole cover story was that I'd been with Chris and
we'd been gone somewhere and Chris was backing up
the story because he was my slave And my work had
called because in the restaurant industry, people
are always calling in sick trying to look for
someone to cover for their shift. And so my the
manager at at either the Nampa or Boisey location,
I believe it was the Nampa location, had been
trying to get a hold of me because they needed
me to cover some shifts that weekend. now that
I was good to just start working all the time.
And my dad was like, "Your work is pissed. You
need to call him. Where have you been?" So, he's
working at covering all this up. So, I call work
and they're like, "Where have you been?" I'm like,
"I guess I was out somewhere." Like, I have no
idea. Oh, it was insane, Emma. And so, yeah. Then
life just went on as normal and I wouldn't begin
to remember these things. And then later, months,
couple months later, it was the fall. I would be
it would be arranged that we would get rid of that
luggage handler guy when my grandpa came back from
his mission for the Mormon church because he'd
been out of town during this whole operation like
I mentioned earlier. And so when he came back from
Texas from his mission, it was the first night
he was back. I I don't believe anyone even knew
he was back. And we went and we got rid of that
guy. And we dressed as Mormon missionaries. There
was four of us. Yep. That's one way we disguise
ourselves is we just straight up dressed
like Mormon missionaries. And so two of us,
me and another younger gentleman who is in a in a
bloodline family and was a trauma-based mindslave
and a friend of mine, David, we went over to
this gentleman's house. We knocked on the door.
Gentleman opened the door. First thing he did was
look at me and said, "You." And he punched me so
hard, Emma. It knocked me out. I got knocked out
right there on his doorstep. And that's a whole
another story for a whole another a whole another
discussion. But we've been talking for quite a
while. I should probably I should probably close
um on these things. So So that was my experience
uh in Japan. There's a lot more in there. People
can read about it in my journaled memories both on
my website or in my book. Um and they're welcome
to. It's Masaru Takum and Kobe Japan. And so it
talks a lot about the manipulations of our world
and how these things occur and the processes and
who's involved and how and how it works. Our last
discussion we talked about blackmail. And so these
blackmailing operations are important for gaining
access to such things as the people who control
the Boisee airport. so that it is an asset to you
and your operations. So these things are being
used in our world, not just in this country,
but globally. And there's a lot going on and
people don't understand it. And so the reason I
talk about these things isn't because I'm trying
to be a rat. I wish that these things we had
done when I was operational were good and that
they were for the benefit of the country and the
people, but they weren't. It was mass murder of
the people in Japan. It was murder of a man, two
men who I can't judge because I don't know. And it
was the murder of an American citizen on American
soil after the event to help cover it all up. It
is so convoluted and so disgusting. Things are
illegal that they're doing unconstitutional and
immoral. They are against God's will. God's intent
was never for his children to lose their free will
and be used in these ways. It's disgusting what
these people who consider themselves to be men of
science or men of religion and God uh magicians
of God. They are disgusting and they need to be
exposed. A lot of these things we just talked
about a lot of classified information. Emma
things that the CIA, Pentagon, and the White
House don't want getting out. That particular
operation was approved by President Bill Clinton.
It was approved by the president. That operation,
it was planned and executed by the Pentagon
through the CIA. And it is disgusting. And
so these things have to be exposed. They're hidden
behind what they consider to be national security.
You have the 1947 National Security Act, which
are covering up the events I just told you about.
You have the 1949 Central Intelligence Agency Act
also actively working at covering it up. These are
laws, mechanisms in the government that are not
they are not invincible through law and through
public awareness. These things can be changed.
We can repeal these laws. We can repeal them.
We can raise such a fuss within our government
that they have to repeal them and that we have
to operate as a nation based on law and
order, not covering up government crime.
So to end, I just want to say there is
hope. He said, "When I go through these
things and through these years, it feels
like I'm just I'm just beating on a brick
wall that must be a hundred feet thick."
But it's not immobile. There is hope. If
we can raise conscious awareness through
these discussions, through our websites,
through our books, then people can become
aware. They can make decisions about how
they want to be ruled by their government.
If they want to be ruled by their government,
if they want to be ruled by the government leaders
who are almost all corrupt and involved with this
disgusting traumabased mind control because it's
not specific to the CIA. It's not specific to the
Pentagon or the White House. It is a huge thing
and these people know about it and shame on them
for not talking about it. Shame on them for not
bringing awareness. If we want national security,
we've got to expose these things. We can do that
through truth, through sharing it, and through
the people getting knowledge. And so I pray for
the soul of this nation. I pray for the people.
And I hope that someday humanity will look back
and say we fixed fix. We have the courage to fix
because if we don't we're done. The soul of
this nation is so I pray that the people can
wake up. we can end this because there's
a lot of stuff. There's a lot going on.
I would advise people to read my website,
buy my book, read it, read Kathy's book,
read Eliza E's book, read Nathan Reynolds
work. There's a lot going on. There's a lot
of information that you can follow. So,
do your research, learn what's going on.
Thank you, Emma. That's my book there. It can
be found at mormonarch.com uh under the section
simply purchase book and I have it up through Lulu
because it's an easy way for me to distribute it
in the population. So you can go there, you can
purchase it. I put it up for sale right now. It's
up for sale through the month of month of July.
I'm able to do that periodically uh in order to
save people cost. So the full price is 2777, but
you just watch for a sale. It'll be on sale or
go to my website. Much of what's in my book is
available for free on my website. If you have a
mind free enough to think for itself and to seek
out this information, it's available. I'll give
it to you. give it to you at no cost other than
it's going to blow your mind and it's going to
shatter your reality. We pray for that and we pray
that people people look into these things because
there's a lot of Thank you. Thank you, Jr. Thank
you for sharing those painful memories with us.
It really shines a light on what's happening
behind the scenes. you know, you're one story
out of thousands, hundreds of thousands, millions
that have went through these programs, you know,
and to hear the types of things that they're
using one person for. And then you think about
all the people in there and the different things
that they're being used for. And it's like almost
inconceivable to think about how much crime is
being done every day using innocent people that
they're taking their lives from. And like you
said, they're not granting them the consent or
the ability to even remember what they're doing.
And so it's really important that we do talk about
this because it's horrible that people don't even
have a say in committing crime and that innocent
lives are being taken to help cover up these
things that they're doing to innocent children
like you. you know, we're we're committing crime
illegally under national security on the backs
of children at the end of the day. And that's a
horrific thought to consider and to think about
how much crime in so many different ways using so
many different innocent people is happening on a
daily basis to protect cowards who like to hurt
kids. Traitors. origin traders. Yes. And your book
is absolutely incredible. If people can purchase
it, I really encourage you to. J.R.'s not in this
to make a ton of money. He's not in this to get
attention. Like he said, he's in this to bring
awareness and it's it's a way to immortalize this
information by purchasing it in a book. You know,
my podcasts have been terminated. They can
terminate websites, but they can't terminate
a book. You know, these are ways that the that
this information can be eternalized and can be
given to other people so they can have it at home
and refer to it and learn. So, I really encourage
you guys to buy buy his book if you can. It is
on Lulu. I'll have that in the show notes. And
then you guys can also get to it through his book,
Mormon Monarch.com. There's just a tab at the top,
purchase book, and then you guys can have access
to all of his memories that he has documented on
here as well. some that we went through today,
others that we went through on other episodes,
some that we haven't talked about at all on
here. So, you guys can can go through this
and learn. Um, he does a phenomenal job breaking
down this. These are long form. Everyone is is
pretty much a book. You know, you could make
a book out of every every memory individually,
but really important stuff and it's a it's a
wonderful way to get to know J.R. Moore. Um,
an easy thing you guys can do, um, like he said,
if a, if purchasing a book is out of your budget,
go through and read those writings that he's, um,
written for us on his website. And then also a
way that you can support him is take the website
whenever you guys click on a memory, go to one,
copy and paste the what the memory if it impacted
you, and go share it on your social media and
talk about it. Bring people to his website. Then
they can find where they can purchase his book.
They can go through and read this. So, it's a
really easy way too if if purchasing the book
isn't something you're able to do, help share his
memories and share it on your social media and
bring people to his to his content. Um, these
are really important memories and information
that he's posting here. So, there's many ways
that you guys can support. I was telling J.R.,
one of the most common things that I get asked
is, "What can I do to help? What can I do to
help?" And of course, supporting Survivors Work is
one way. Sharing these podcast episodes is another
and others that they do on other platforms, but a
lot of survivors have websites, they have blogs,
and sharing that can be instrumental in helping
drive traffic to them so that way other people
can find their work and we can educate more
people on this. So, if you guys could do that,
that would mean the world to me. I'm going to
have his website. It's just www.mormanmonarch.com.
Um, I'll have that in the show notes. You guys can
type that in your search bar as well. it's pretty
easy to find. Um, but please share his website and
help bring awareness. Please share his book. Um,
again, even if you guys can't purchase it
at this time, and especially if you do,
post the link to his book so other people can
find it and help promote it. Um, really really
e ways that you guys can support. There's always
a way that we can support either for free or very
little money. So, I really encourage you guys to
purchase this. Um, for those people listening,
I will be doing a contest um that I'll announce
on my social media giving away a free book of
J.R.'s that he was so generous to donate. So, I'll
have that as well and I'm excited to do that. So,
keep an eye out. Follow me on I'll
have it on YouTube. I'll announce it
um and on my social media pages, my Twitter,
my Instagram, um my Facebook. I'll have a
contest that I'll run alongside Jr. and we'll
be giving away a free copy of his book to one
of you. So stay tuned for that as well. Um and
then J.R. is there anything else that you wanted
to share or close with today before we wrap
up? Thank you, Emma. I really appreciate it.
I appreciate your time. I appreciate everything
that you do to help bring light to these things
because without people like you, without
without people trying to help in this fight,
you know, so thank you. Really appreciate. Thank
you to all your viewers. Chatted with some of them
online before and they wonder. Thank you. It's
my great honor and I'm so happy that more and
more people are finding you and supporting you and
it's it's wonderful to have you on. I wish and I
can't wait to have conversations about you getting
justice and you know more positive things but in
its own way talking about these horrible things is
serving a really positive impact that's going to
last the test of time and hopefully create a big
impact either now in in small ripples or in big
ways in the future, you know. So no matter what,
just talking about this is creating an impact and
and it is a wonderful thing. Even though it's
so difficult and hard to hear these things,
to contend with them, and of course on your end to
talk about them. So I'm grateful to have you here,
J.R. you're welcome on anytime. We can't
wait to have you back. Like I said,
you're so beloved by our community and
appreciated. And for everybody listening,
like J.R. said, we couldn't do this without you
guys. you guys are really the cornerstone of
helping move the the snowball and and help this
movement grow. You know, we could talk here,
but if we had nobody listening, you know,
we'd just be talking into a void. So,
I really appreciate you guys reaching out to
J.R. and encouraging him or sharing how he
impacted you or or your own puzzle pieces to
contribute to his story. You guys can connect
with him right on his page. He has a contact tab
as well. So, if you guys want to reach out to him,
um I forgot to mention that you guys can connect
with him right from his website. And I encourage
you guys to even if it's just uh you know how
he's impacted you and and you know sharing some
words of encouragement to him, that can go a
really far way too. So, I'll have all those
links in the show notes. You guys stay tuned
for a contest to win a free copy of J.R's book.
I'm really excited to do this alongside him. We
couldn't do this without you guys. Like I said,
thank you with all of our hearts. God bless
you all and we will see you next time.